(Leonard:)What if...
what if this is the thing
(Leonard:)that would've finally let him
open that bottle of champagne?
(Raj:)Maybe he didn't know what
to pair champagne with.
(Raj:)Strawberries, caviar, oysters.
All good choices.
(Raj:)Yeah, that look right there
(Raj:)is why people eat before
they come to your parties.
(Leonard:)This has to mean something.
(Howard:)Well, there's no discernible
pattern that I can see,
(Howard:)but it shouldn't be too hard
to run the numbers and check.
(Leonard:)Well, maybe we can get
some time on the supercomputer.
(Howard:)Sure. We could try
multiple regressions
(Howard:)with varying physical and
experimental constants.
(Leonard:)Oh, we could run
a pattern-matching algorithm
(Leonard:)against well-known
unsolved physics problems.
(Howard:)Ooh, it might be
a substitution cipher.
(Howard:)We could start
with basic cryptanalysis.
(Raj:)Or we could talk to this guy
he used to share an office with.
(Howard:)Oh, let's do that.
(Leonard:)Because you don't know how
to do cryptanalysis, do you?
(Howard:)I'm not even sure if
it's the right word.